Guide to the Pittsburgh Public School Records AIS.1966.18a
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Hancock Sub-District, 1871-1939
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Bessie Prosser, February 1927- June 1927 (Folder 22)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Bessie Prosser, 1933-1934 (Folder 23)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Bessie Prosser, July 1927 (Folder 24)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Bessie Prosser and Blanche Pollock, July 1927 (Folder 25)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Ida Rosenbloom, 1927-1928 (Folder 26)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Ida Rosenbloom, 1932-1934 (Folder 27)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Ida Rosenbloom, 1934-1936 (Folder 28)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Ida Rosenbloom, undated (Folder 29)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, Summer 1928 (Folder 30)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, 1927 (Folder 31)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, 1927 (Folder 32)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, 1927 (Folder 33)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book (Promoted to High School), 1927 (Folder 34)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, February 1931 (Folder 35)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, 1931 (Folder 36)
  - Immigrant School, Teacher's Record Book, undated (Folder 37)
- Highland Sub-District (Margaretta, Peabody, Garfield, Fulton and Brilliant), 1869-1929
  - Treasurer's Cash Book, 1890-1907
  - Board Minute Book, 1869-1885
  - Board Minute Book, 1885-1894
  - Board Minute Book, 1894-1899
  - Board Minute Book, 1899-1910
  - Board Minute Book, June 1910- January 1912
  - Expense Reports (3), February 1907-February 1908 (Folder 1)
  - Receipt from Bernard Gloekler Company, January 1910 (Folder 2)
  - Peabody School
    - Principal's Diary: Georgia Stoney, 1912-1916
    - Peabody: Evening, 1923-1929
- Homewood Sub-District, 1875-1911
  - Board Minute Books, 1875-1888
  - Board Minute Books, January 1898- January 1904
  - Board Minute Books, 1911
- Howard Sub District (Park, Bloomfield and Woolslayer), 1877-1911
  - Board Minute Books, 1877-1885
  - Board Minute Books, 1885-1894
  - Board Minute Books, 1894-1897
  - Board Minute Books, 1899-1901
  - Board Minute Books, 1901-1904
  - Board Minute Books, 1908-1911
  - Board Minute Books, 1911
  - Treasurer's Checks, 1889-1890 (Folder 1)
- Humboldt Sub-District, 1866-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1866-1893
  - Board Minute Book, 1908-1911
  - Letter from the School Board, Ripped, Undated (Folder 1)
- Knox Sub-District, 1898-1926
  - Board Minutes Book, March 1898- November 1911
  - Board Minutes (2 Pages), 1926 (Folder 1)
  - Letter from St. Clair Savings & Trust Company, 1926 (Folder 2)
- Lawrence Sub-District, 1905-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1905-1911
- Liberty Sub District (Liberty, Shakespeare, Osceola and Friendship), 1904-1911
  - Board Minute Book, July 1904- December 1908
  - Board Minute Book, June 1909- December 1911
  - Mailings & Payroll List, 1911 (Folder 1)
- Lincoln Sub-District (Lincoln, Lemington, and Larimer), 1855-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1899-1904
  - Board Minute Book, 1904-1910
  - Board Minute Book, 1901-1911
  - Ledger, 1896-1904
  - Ledger, 1910-1911
  - Deeds and Bonds, 1855-1908 (Folder 1)
  - Mailings and Bonds, 1855-1908 (Folder 2)
- Luckey Sub-District (Woodville and Sweetbriar), 1903-1911
  - Board Minute Book, March 1903- November 1911
- Minersville Sub-District (Minersville, 33rd, Webster and Rose), 1908-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1908-1911
- Monongahela Sub-District, 1907-1911
  - Board Minute Book, May 1907-November 1911
- Montooth Sub-District, 1897-1911
  - Board Minute Book, May 1897- November 1911
  - Blank Forms, undated (Folder 1)
- Moorhead Sub-District (Granville and Miller), 1880-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1880-1902
  - Board Minute Book, 1902-1907
  - Board Minute Book, 1907
  - Board Minute Book, 1911
  - Letter from Lawrence Barnum & Co., 1907 (Folder 1)
- Morse Sub-District, 1875-1912
  - Board Minute Book, 1879-1894
  - Board Minute Book, 1894-1907
  - Board Minute Book, 1907-1912
  - Treasurer's Book, 1875-1912
- Mount Albion Sub-District (McCandless, McCleary, Mt. Albion, Sunnyside, and Morningside), 1900-1911
  - Board Minute Book, May 1906- December 1911
  - Cash Book, 1900-1903
  - Cash Book, 1903-1911
- Mount Washington Sub-District (Mt. Washington, Whittier, Cargo)
  - Mailings, Notes, and Bond (Folder 1)
- North Sub-District, 1843-1910
  - Board Minute Book, 1843-1868
  - Board Minute Book, 1868-1887
  - Board Minute Book, 1901-1910
- Oakland Sub-District (Soho and Bellefield), 1906-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1906-1911
- Peebles Sub-District (2nd Ave (Hazelwood), Greenfield, Squirrel Hill, Brown's, Glenwood, and Logan), 1879-1912
  - Board Minute Books, 1879-1911
  - Board Minute Books, 1911-1912
  - Principals Monthly Reports, 1887-1903
  - Miscellaneous Administrative Documents (Folder 1)
- Ralston Sub-District, 1847-1912
  - Board Minute Book, 1847-1862
  - Board Minute Book, 1908-1911
  - Principal's Report, September 1856-June 1868
  - Treasurer's Cash Book, 1872-1912
  - Minutes of Special Meeting of the Board (1 page), August 1911
- Reserve Township, 1836-1887
  - Board Minute Book, 1836-1861
  - Board Minute Book, 1863-1887
  - Board Minute Book, undated
  - Account Book, June 1863- August 1877
- Riverside Sub-District, 1894-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1894-1911
- South Sub-District, 1883-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1883-1911
- Springfield Sub-District, 1870-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1870-1887
  - Board Minute Book, 1887-1905
  - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
  - Financial Documents, July 1904 (Folder 1)
- Saint Clair Borough (Jefferson, Brashear, Bane), 1871-1923
  - Board Minute Book, 1871-1885
  - Board Minute Book, 1904-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1917-1923
  - Tax Book, 1921
  - Treasurer's Cash Book, 1919-1923
  - Audit Legal Papers, 1922 (Folder 1)
- Sheridanville, 1899-1912
  - Examination Records, 1899-1901
  - Examination Records, 1901-1903
  - Examination Records, 1903-1904
  - Examination Records, 1904-1905
  - Examination Records, 1905-1906
  - Examination Records, 1906-1907
  - Examination Records, 1907
  - Examination Records, 1906-1908
  - Examination Records, 1908-1909
  - Examination Records, 1909-1910
  - Examination Records, 1910-1911
  - Examination Records, 1911-1912
- Spring Garden Borough, 1883-1917
  - Board Minute Book, 1883-1901
  - Board Minute Book, 1901-1915
  - Board Minute Book, 1915-1920
  - Treasurer's Cash Book, 1911-1920
  - Teacher's Monthy Reports, 1901-1907
  - Teacher's Monthly Reports, 1904-1906
  - Teacher's Monthly Reports, 1905-1911
  - Teacher's Monthly Reports, 1911-1917
  - Teacher's Monthly Reports, 1911-1920
  - Teacher's Monthly Reports, 1917-1920
  - Loose Board Minutes, 1915-1917
- Sterrett Township (Sterrett and Linden), 1888-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1888-1903
  - Board Minute Book, 1903-1906
  - Board Minute Book, 1904-1911
  - Account Book, 1901-1903
  - Miscellaneous Administrative and Financial Documents (Folder 1)
- Thaddeus Stevens Sub-District, 1901-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1901-1911
- Washington Sub-District (Washington on Fortieth, Main and Hatfield), 1865-1912
  - Board Minute Book, 1865-1878
  - Board Minute Book, 1890-1897
  - Board Minute Book, 1907-1912
  - Examination Records, 1887-1889
  - Examination Records, 1890-1891
  - Examination Records, 1892
  - Examination Records, 1893
  - Examination Records, 1895
  - Examination Records, 1896-1898
  - Principal's Report, 1873-1876
  - Principal's Report, 1876-1879
  - Principal's Report, 1879-1883
  - Principal's Report, 1883-1887
  - Principal's Report, 1888-1893
  - Register, 1910-1914 (Folder 1)
- Westlake Sub-District, 1899-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1899-1906
  - Board Minute Book, 1906-1991
- Westwood Borough, 1913-1926
  - Board Minute Books, 1913-1915
  - Board Minute Books, 1915-1921
  - Board Minute Books, 1921-1926
  - Teacher Contracts (Folder 1)
- West Liberty Sub-District, 1909-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1909-1911
- Wickersham Sub-District, 1869-1911
  - Board Minute Book, 1869-1887
  - Board Minute Book, 1887-1894
  - Board Minute Book, 1894-1907
  - Board Minute Book, 1907-1911
  - Financial, Insurance, and Maintenance Documents, 1905-1911 (Folder 1)